

Software Developer

💌 volkan.ozturkis@hotmail.com 📞 05398124873 😲 Çankaya/ANKARA

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/volkanöztürk/ 🜎 https://github.com/cevolkan-ozturk 🚗 B 🙎 Male

ABOUT ME

I graduated from Atatürk University Civil Engineering Department in 2014 as a high honor student. I completed my master's degree with thesis in Geotechnical science at Eskisehir Technical University in 2023. I completed my military service as a Civil Engineer at Hakkari Provincial Gendarmerie Command. 6 years in the construction industry, Civil Control Engineer, Field engineer, etc. I have worked in various positions. Afterwards, then I decided to change careers and stepped into the software industry. In order to be successful in this sector, I participated in the Information Technologies Certificate Program given by METU Computer Engineering and this program is a compressed form of computer engineering. I have successfully completed this certificate program. I received the ISTQB Foundation Level, the most important certificate in the field of test engineering with international validity. In addition to this trainings, I try to get training, practice and meet the requirements of the software industry on different platforms (Udemy, Btk Akademi, Linkedin Learning, Hackerank, Patika.dev). I want to improve myself by working in a good company with my education and skills in the informatics and software sector and thus add value to the company I work for and myself. In my future career, I always aim to develop software that offers the easiest, highest quality, most effective and simplest solution by using up-to-date technologies. I am currently looking for a job.

EDUCATION

Master Degree, Eskisehir Technical University 09/2020 - 06/2023 | Eskişehir, TURKEY **Geotechical Engineering**

ODTÜ 11/2021 - 10/2022 | Ankara, TURKEY

336-hour INFORMATION

TECHNOLOGIES CERTIFICATE PROGRAM

Bachelor's Degree, Atatürk University 09/2010 - 06/2014 | Erzurum, Türkiye

Civil Engineering

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

.NET Bootcamp Student, Simpra/Patika.dev

04/2023 - 06/2023

.NET, ASP.NET Core, C#, Entity Framework, Visual Studio, OOP, Web Services API, SQL

Etstur Java Bootcamp Student, <i>Coderspace</i> Java SE, Spring Boot, Rest Api, Hibernate, JPA, Swagger, Postman, H2 [09/2022 – 11/2022 DB, Mysql, Solid
Site Civil Engineer, Osman Acar İnşaat	07/2021 - 09/2021
Civil Engineer, Teknik Sistem Yapı Denetim Limited Şirketi	09/2016 - 07/2021
Reserve Officer Civil Engineer, TSK (Türk Silahlı Kuvvetleri	11/2014 – 11/2015 Hakkari, Turkey
Civil Engineering Intern, Limak Group of Companies	08/2013 – 10/2013 Ankara, Turkey
Civil Enginnering Intern, Yüksel Proje Uluslararası A.Ş.	06/2012 – 09/2012 Kırsehir, Turkey

SKILLS

Java, Python, SQL, JavaScript, HTML5, CSS, C#, .NET, Github, Spring Farmework, Back-End Web Development, Postman API, Swagger API, Flutter, MySQL, AutoCAD, Microsoft Office, Plaxis 2D, Plaxis 3D, Slide, SAP 2000, İdeCAD

LANGUAGES

English $\bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet$ Turkish $\bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet$

CERTIFICATES

- MICROSOFT PROJECT® ile Uygulamalı İş Programı Hazırlanması ve Zaman Çizelgesi Yönetimi
- YABANCI DİL KURSU (İNGİLİZCE)
- 336-hour INFORMATION TECHNOLOGIES CERTIFICATE PROGRAM - METU
- MOBİLE DEVELOPMENT WİTH FLUTTER BİLGİ TEKNOLOJİLERİ KURUMU
- BACK END WEB DEVELOPMENT WITH BEGINNER JAVA - PATIKA.DEV
- TEMEL İŞ SAĞLIĞI VE GÜVENLİĞİ EĞİTİM BELGESİ

- ISTQB Foundation Level (CTFL) Turkish Testing Board ☑
- YAZILIM TEST OTOMASYONU BTK Akademi
- JAVA BOOTCAMP ETSTUR-CODERSPACE
- SOFTWARE TESTING EXPERTISE UDEMY
- CARRER PATHS FOR SOFTWARE PATİKA.DEV

REFERENCES

Burak EVİRGEN, *Asst. Prof. Dr.*, Eskisehir Technical University burakevirgen@eskisehir.edu.tr

Süleyman TEZCAN, *Company Manager*, Teknik Sistem Yapı Denetim Ltd. Şti. stezcan40@gmail.com, 05444626545

İsmail ESKİOĞLU, *General Manager*, KIRŞEHİR ORGANİZE SANAYİ MÜDÜRLÜĞÜ ismail.eskioglu.40@gmail.com, 05372357237

Yiğit KARALI, *Construction Supervisor*, OTOYOL İŞLETME A.Ş. fethullah_1266@hotmail.com, 05343433570

INTERESTS

Reading science-fiction, fantasy novels and article, Fitness and swimming